A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Chief Information Officer of the Virginia Information Technologies Agency, 1981-2021
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Correspondence and subject files of the Chief Information Officer of the Virginia Information Technologies Agency, 1981-2021
The Library of Virginia
53612
5 cu. ft. (5 boxes)
Virginia Information Technologies Agency
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Accession 53612 transferred by the Virginia Information Technologies Agency, 5 May 2022.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Virginia Information Technologies Agency (VITA) was approved by the General Assembly on 2 April 2003 during Governor Mark R. Warner's administration to provide information technology that enables the government to better serve the public. VITA serves as the Commonwealth's consolidated, centralized information technology organization. The newly created agency superseded the Department of Information Technology and the Department of Technology Planning. Its responsibilities include the operation of information technology infrastructure for the executive branch agencies, the governance of information technology investments, and the procurement of technology on behalf of other state agencies and institutions of higher learning. The Information Technology Investment Board (ITIB) was created along with VITA to review and prioritize enterprise-wide technology investments across state government. The Board is also responsible for appointing the Chief Information Officer (CIO) to serve as VITA's chief administrative officer.
Responsibility for the 911 Services Board and the Virginia Geographic Information Network Advisory Board was transferred from VITA to the Virginia Dept. of Emergency Services in 2020 (HB 1003, Chap. 423, approved March 23, 2020).
Chief Information Officers include: Lemuel C. Stewart, Jr., 2003-2009; Samuel Nixon, Jr., 2010-2015; Nelson P. Moe, 2015-2020.
Scope and Content
Correspondence and Subject Files of the Chief Information Officer, 1981-2021, consists of 5 boxes and is arranged in original order. These records document the planning, administrative activities, functions, major achievements and initiatives, and the implementation of agency programs, and are evidence of actions and policy decisions. Contains Chronological correspondence of the Director, 2004-2020; Presentations, 2004-2021; and Reports and subject files, 1981-2019. Includes correspondence, agreements, conference materials, memoranda, plans, presentations, reports and studies.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the original order.
Contents List
- Correspondence and subject files of the Chief Information Officer, 1981-2021.
  - Dept. of Information Technology (DIT) - Agency Head memoranda, 1981-1990. (Box 1)
  - Dept. of Information Technology (DIT) - Correspondence, 1993-2003. (Box 1)
  - Cheryl Clark correspondence (DIT and VITA Executive), 2002-2004. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Cheryl Clark and Lemuel C. Stewart, Jr., 2003 Nov-2004 Mar. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Lemuel C. Stewart, Jr., 2004 Apr-2004 Dec. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Lemuel C. Stewart, Jr., 2005. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Lemuel C. Stewart, Jr., 2006 Jan-June. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Lemuel C. Stewart, Jr., 2006 July-Dec. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Lemuel C. Stewart, Jr., 2007. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Lemuel C. Stewart, Jr., 2008. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Lemuel C. Stewart, Jr. and Interim CIO Leonard Pomata, 2009 Jan-June. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Interim CIO Leonard Pomata and George F. Coulter, 2009 July-Dec. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Samuel Nixon, Jr., 2010. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Samuel Nixon, Jr., 2011 Jan-Feb. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Samuel Nixon, Jr., 2011 Mar-Apr. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Samuel Nixon, Jr., 2011 May-Dec. (Box 1)
  - Chronological file: Samuel Nixon, Jr., 2012. (Box 2)
  - Chronological file: Samuel Nixon, Jr., 2013. (Box 2)
  - Chronological file: Samuel Nixon, Jr., 2014. (Box 2)
  - Chronological file: Samuel Nixon, Jr., Interim CIO Eric Link, and Nelson P. Moe, 2015. (Box 2)
  - Chronological file: Nelson P. Moe, 2016. (Box 2)
  - Chronological file: Nelson P. Moe, 2017. (Box 2)
  - Chronological file: Nelson P. Moe, 2018. (Box 2)
  - Chronological file: Nelson P. Moe, 2019. (Box 2)
  - Chronological file: Nelson P. Moe, 2020. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Large Agency Transition Team Kickoff meeting, 2004 June 24. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Geographic Information System (GIS) Town Hall meeting #5 Shared Services Analysis, 2004 Nov 22. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: IT in the Commonwealth - Transforming the Business of Government to the Commonwealth of Virginia Innovative Technology Symposium (COVITS), 2005 Sept 19. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Chief Financial Officer Status Report, 2005 Oct 18. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Supplier Management Staff Augmentation (SMSA) Update, 2005 Nov 17. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: A 21st Century Partnership to Transform IT in the Commonwealth to the Information Technology Association of America (ITAA-INPUT) breakfast, 2005 Dec 6. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Infrastructure Partnership to the Commonwealth Competition Council, 2006 Jan 10. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Greater Richmond Technology Council, 2006 Jan 20. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Introduction to VITA and Infrastructure PPEA (Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act of 2002) - Cabinet briefing, 2006 Jan 23. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: VITA and Infrastructure PPEA (Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act of 2002) - Governor Timothy Kaine briefing, 2006 Feb 13. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: ITAA-INPUT (Information Technology Association of America), 2006 Feb 15. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Welcome to the Honorable William H. Leighty, Chief of Staff, Office of Governor Timothy Kaine, to the Agency Head and Agency Information Technology Resource (AITR) meeting, 2006 Feb 16. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: VITA-Northrop Grumman (NG) Transition/Transformation - Cabinet briefing, 2006 June 19. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Supplier Diversity Initiative Update (SWaM) - CIO Report to Governor Kaine, 2006 Aug 18. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Commonwealth Agency Information Technology Resource (AITR) Communications Exchange to the Commonwealth AITR meeting, 2006 Oct 23. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Commonwealth Agency Information Technology Resource (AITR) Communications Exchange to the Commonwealth AITR meeting, 2006 Dec 16. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: To Rappahannock Westminster-Canterbury, 2007 Apr 2. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: The Power of Partnership, to the Virginia Association for Mapping and Land Information Systems (VAMLIS) Conference, 2007 May 7. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Information Technology Structure in Virginia, to a Virginia Tech Master of Information Sciences class, 2007 Oct 30. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: State of Information in the Commonwealth, 2007. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: VITA Report, 2008 Feb 20. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Budget Cuts and IT Contingent Labor (ITCL), 2009. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Commonwealth of Virginia IT Finances, 2010 Nov 13. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Employee Dialogue, 2014 Jan 30. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Internal Technology and Portfolio Management (ITPM) - Portfolio Update, 2014 June. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: VITA Update, 2014 June. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: IT Infrastructure Partnership, Disaster Recovery (DR) Services - CIO Brief, 2015 June. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Project Management Division Overview for CIO, 2015 June. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Relationship Management Governance (RMG) Division, 2015 June 9. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: CIO Overview - Internal Technology and Portfolio Management (ITMP), 2015 June 11. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Administration and Finance for CIO, 2015 June 11. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: VITA Communications, 2015 June 19. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Executive Team Update - Status of VITA Work Plan Portfolio, 2025 June 25. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Comprehensive Infrastructure Agreement (CIA) Services Agreement Briefing to CIO (Parts I and II), 2015 June-July. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: CIO Council Survey Results, 2015 July 15. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Supply Chain Management, 2015 July. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Unisys Mainframe Update, 2015 July 21. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: IT Contingent Labor (ITCL) Contract Overview, 2015 July 24. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Overview of VITA Rate Development Methodology and Process, 2015 Aug 6. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Executive Team (ET) Update - Status of VITA Work Plan Portfolio, 2015 Aug 27. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Recommended Technology Investment Portfolio (RTIP) Report, 2015 Nov. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Information Technology Resource Management (ITRM) Policies, Standards and Guidelines (PSG) - Enterprise Architecture, 2015 Dec. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: IT Infrastructure Services Sourcing, 2015-2016. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Service Management Group (SMG), 2015-2016. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: VITA Update to Agency Leadership - Sourcing Strategy, 2016 Jan. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Project Management Division (PMD) Project Status - Dept. of Human Resource Management (DHRM) Personnel Management Information System (PMIS) Migration from Unisys, 2016 Jan-Feb. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Telecommunication Expense Management Billing Solutions (TEBS) Project - Issue briefing, 2016 Feb 3. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Workplace Productivity Services (WPS) Technical Support and Overview, 2016 Feb 22. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: IT Infrastructure Services Sourcing, 2016 Mar 24. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: VITA and IT Sourcing, 2016 Mar 31. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: VITA IT Sourcing Update - Secretaries of Technology and Secretary of Finance, and Dept. of Planning and Budget (DPB) briefing, 2016 Aug 10. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Recommended Technology Investment Projects (RTIP) Report, 2016 Nov 28. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: Revision of IT Investment Management Standard (2016), 2017 Jan 31. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: VITA Enterprise Information Architecture Program - Background and Current Initiatives, 2017 Oct 17. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: IT Governance - Managing Technology Investments to Provide Value to Citizens in Virginia, 2018 Apr 26. (Box 2)
  - Presentation: IT Governance - Managing Technology Investements Approach brief, Dept. of Social Services submission of Decision Brief of Administration, 2021 July 7. (Box 2)
  - Computer System Evaluation Report, Virginia ADP Cost Determination Report - Prepared by Office of Audit, Office of Inspector General, US Dept. of Labor, 1980 May 9. (Box 3)
  - Final Report and Recommendatios for the Commonwealth of Virginia (COV) Telecommunications - Contract No. 1228601, prepared by Federal Engineering, Inc. (FE), 1987. (Box 3)
  - Computer Services Operations Study - Summary of Final Report, prepared for Dept. of Information Technology (DIT) by Technology Planning and Management Corp. (TPMC), 1992 July 3. (Box 3)
  - Computer Services Operations Study - Final Report, prepared for Dept. of Information Technology by TPMC, 1992 Aug 31. (Box 3)
  - State of Virginia Dept. of Information Technology Enterprise Operations Center - A Comparative Benchmark Annual Report, prepared by Gartner Group, 1999 Sept. (Box 3)
  - Council on Technology Services (COTS) - Annual Report, 1999. (Box 3)
  - Dept. of Information Technology (DIT) Planning World - Resource Planning Monthly Report, 2001 Dec. (Box 3)
  - Dept. of Information Technology (DIT) - Proposed Business Plan Initiative Fiscal Year 2002, Funding Required, 2001 Apr-May. (Box 3)
  - eGovernment Readiness Assessment of DIT, prepared by Price Waterhouse Coopers, 2001 June. (Box 3)
  - DIT - The Future of Enterprise Information Technology in Virginia, 2002 Mar. (Box 3)
  - Formation of DIT Expenses FY 2002, 2002. (Box 3)
  - VITA Business Plan, 2002-2006. (Box 3)
  - Executive Summary of DIT Financial Position, 2003 June 30. (Box 3)
  - VITA Final Operating Plan (two folders), 2003 Aug 29. (Box 3)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts (APA) - Correspondence, 2003-2004. (Box 3)
  - IT Transformation Financial Benefits (Cost Savings) Updates, 2004-2006. (Box 3)
  - Chief Information Officer - Thirty Day Status Report, 2004 Feb 25. (Box 3)
  - Lemeul C. Stewart, Jr. - Interview with America's Network Magazine, 2004 Apr. (Box 3)
  - Performance Leadership Retreat - Council on Virginia's Future, 2004 Oct 19. (Box 3)
  - Circuit Court Certifications of Security Compliance, 2004. (Box 3)
  - Dept. of Human Resources (DHRM) - Classification Review of VITA Positions, 2004. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Fusion Center: Statewide Alert Network (SWAN) - Virginia Dept. of Emergency Management (VDEM) and Virginia State Police (VSP), 2004. (Box 3)
  - Agency Strategic Plans (two folders), 2004. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Information Providers Network (VIPNet), 2004-2005. (Box 3)
  - CIO Employment - Lemuel C. Stewart, Jr. and George F. Coulter, 2004 Jan-2009 Dec. (Box 3)
  - Reports Required by VITA, CIO, or Information Technology Investment Board (ITIB), 2005 Jan 6. (Box 3)
  - VITA Customer Service Survey - Report of Results, prepared by University of Virginia Center for Survey Research and UVA Welden Cooper Center for Public Service, 2005. (Box 3)
  - Homeland Security in Virginia - George Foresman and VITA papers, 2005-2006. (Box 3)
  - Trends in VITA Revenue from State Agencies, 2006-2009. (Box 3)
  - VITA-Northrop Grumman (NG) Transition / Transformation - Cabinet briefing, 2006 Jan 23. (Box 3)
  - Statewide IP Network - VITA / Virginia Tech / University of Virginia Talks, 2006 Feb 1. (Box 3)
  - Customer Relationship Management (CRM) - How It Should Work, 2006 Feb 15. (Box 3)
  - VITA Enterprise Information Dashboard, 2006 Mar 10. (Box 3)
  - Governor's Leadership Forum, 2006 Apr 27. (Box 3)
  - VITA 3.0 Succession Planning Organization Chart, 2006 Aug 7. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Employment Commission - Memorandum of Understanding, 2006 Aug 17. (Box 3)
  - Lemuel C. Stewart, Jr. article - Watershed Moment, Public CIO, 2006 Dec 18. (Box 3)
  - Comprehensive Infrastructure Agreement (CIA) - Detailed Transition Plan (two folders), 2006 June 16. (Box 3)
  - NG and VITA Partnership: Day One, 2006 July 10-11. (Box 3)
  - CH Transition Phase Contractual Deliverables - 2006 Jan-June Final Version and Client Acceptance (four folders), 2006 Aug 26. (Box 3)
  - Gartner Relationship Performance Assessment (RPA) Final Report, 2014. (Box 3)
  - Integris Reports: CIA Contract Review (Apr); Sourcing Option Report (Oct); Final Recommendations Report (Nov), 2015. (Box 3)
  - Independent Accountants' Report on Applying- Agreed-Upon Procedures - Deloitte and Touche, LLP (DTL), 2007 July 1-2008 June 30. (Box 3)
  - Independent Accountants' Report on Applying Agreed-Upon Procedures (DTL) Contract Year 4 Financial Audit, 2009 July 1-2010 June 30. (Box 3)
  - Independent Accountants' Report on Applying Agreed-Upon Procedures (DTL) Contract Year 4 Operational Audit, 2010 Oct 19. (Box 3)
  - Independent Accountants' Report on Applying Agreed-Upon Procedures (DTL) Contract Year 5 Financial Audit as defined by the Comprehensive Infrastructure Agreement (CIA), 2010 July 1-2011 June 30. (Box 3)
  - Independent Accountants' Report on Applying Agreed-Upon Procedures (DTL) Contract Year 5 Operational Audit as defined by the CIA, 2011 Oct 21. (Box 3)
  - Independent Accountants' Report on Applying Agreed-Upon Procedures (DTL) Contract Year 6 Financial Audit as defined by CIA, 2011 July 1-2012 June 30. (Box 3)
  - Independent Accountants' Report on Applying Agreed-Upon Procedures (DTL) Contract Year 6 Operational Audit as defined by CIA, 2012 Sept 20. (Box 3)
  - Independent Accountants' Report on Applying Agreed-Upon Procedures (DTL) Contract Year 7 Financial Audit as defined by CIA, 2012 July 1-2013 June 30. (Box 3)
  - Commonwealth Enterprise Solutions Center (CESC) - Furnishing Plan and Project Review, 2006. (Box 4)
  - VITA Cost Allocation Plan (CAP), US Dept. of Health and Human Services, Office of Cost Allocation Concerns, 2006. (Box 4)
  - Statewide Interoperability Executive Committee (SIEC), 2006-2007. (Box 4)
  - Telework in the Commonwealth, 2006-2008. (Box 4)
  - VITA Benefits Realization 2007: Agency Performance and Recommendations (Parts I-VI), 2007 Apr 18. (Box 4)
  - VITA Benefits Realization 2007, Vol. II: Part VII Metric Information Sheets, 2007 Apr 18. (Box 4)
  - The 9th Annual Commonwealth of Virginia Innovative Technology Symposium (COVITS), 2007 Sept. (Box 4)
  - Agency Information Technology Resource (AITR) Communications Exchange meeting, 2007 Oct 12. (Box 4)
  - VITA General and Administrative Cost Analysis and Comparison Final Report, prepared by Gartner, 2007 Oct 11. (Box 4)
  - Lemuel C. Stewart, Jr. Interview with National Association of State Chief Information Officers (NASCIO), 2007. (Box 4)
  - Change Management and Stategy Execution, 2007. (Box 4)
  - VITA Budget and New Rates, 2007. (Box 4)
  - VITA Program and Budget Brief, 2007. (Box 4)
  - VITA SWaM Report through 2007 June; Integrated Services Program Business Plan (2007 Jan); Draft Proposed Motion (2007 Apr 19), 2007. (Box 4)
  - Governor Kaine's Management Scorecard, 2007. (Box 4)
  - The Virginia Information Technology Infrastructure Partnership Annual Report, 2007-2008. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Taxation - Enterprise Architecture exception request to pilot test Exchange/Outlook 2007 in a production environment, 2007-2008. (Box 4)
  - Virginia Statewide Comprehensive 911 Plan - Next Generation and Beyond, 2008 Jan. (Box 4)
  - Public-Private Education Facilities and Infrastructure Act (PPEA) of 2002 as amended - Guidelines and Procedures, 2008 Jan 17. (Box 4)
  - Virginia Enterprise Applications Program (VEAP) Steering Committee, 2008 Jan 31. (Box 4)
  - Enterprise Architecture - VITA Summary Report, 2008 Jan 31. (Box 4)
  - Delighting the Customer: How VITA and NGIT Can Drive Higher Customer Satisfaction, prepared by ITSMA, 2008 June. (Box 4)
  - IT Infrastructure Partnership: Altiris Security, 2008 June 5. (Box 4)
  - VITA Telework Review - Internal Audit Services Report, 2008 June 30. (Box 4)
  - Continuity of Operations Plan (COOP) for VITA, 2008 July. (Box 4)
  - IT Infrastructure Partnership: Disaster Recovery Services - Expanded Services, 2008 Aug 26. (Box 4)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) Briefing - Interim Review of VITA, 2008 Dec 8. (Box 4)
  - The Governor's Plan for Workforce Development, Workforce Investment Act, State Partner Memorandum of Instruction and Understandings, Comprehensive One Stop Workforce Centers, 2008. (Box 4)
  - National Association of State Chief Information Officers (NASCIO) - Conference and Virginia Recognition Awards Nominations, 2008. (Box 4)
  - The Commonwealth of Virginia Innovation Hub - A Standards Based Open Platform for Government Shared Services, prepared by Oracle, 2008. (Box 4)
  - CIO Reports, 2008. (Box 4)
  - VITA Benefits, 2004-2007. (Box 4)
  - Higher Education Memorandum of Understanding for Information Technology - George Mason University, James Madison University, Old Dominion University, Radford University, and Virginia Military Institute, 2008-2009. (Box 4)
  - Agency Risk Management and Internal Control Standards Compliance, 2008-2010, 2013. (Box 4)
  - Virginia State Police / Virginia Dept. of Emergency Management Transformation, 2009. (Box 4)
  - Report on Amendment 60 - Comprehensive IT Infrastructure Agreement Activities, Progress and Performance, 2010 June 10. (Box 4)
  - The VITA Organization, 2010 June 30. (Box 4)
  - Cost Recovery Structure for IT Services - Letters (rate increase letters), 2010 July 14. (Box 4)
  - Report of Financial Condition for the Fiscal Year Ended June 30, 2011, 2011 Oct 11. (Box 4)
  - Acknowledgement of Notification of Provisions for the Appropriation Act Relating to Indebtedness of State Agencies, Dept. of Planning and Budget, 2011-2016. (Box 4)
  - VITA Workplan, 2012. (Box 4)
  - Agency Preparedness Assessment - Top Performer 2012, from the Office of the Secretary of Veterans Affairs and Homeland Security, 2013 Feb 6. (Box 4)
  - Memorandum of Understanding - VITA, 2013 Apr 22. (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth Data Standardization Final Plan - Reported Pursuant to Item 427 of the 2012 Appropriations Act, 2013 July 1. (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth Enterprise Information Architecture (EIA) Strategy, 2014-2020, 2013 July 1. (Box 4)
  - 10th Anniversary VITA - Event invitations, 2013. (Box 4)
  - National Association of State Chief Information Officers (NASCIO) - Recognition awards nominations and communication plan, 2013. (Box 4)
  - Telecommunication Expense Management and Billing (TES) - Agency Information Technology Resource (AITR) meeting and communication plan, 2013. (Box 4)
  - Article - Virginia's Identity Verification to Reduce Fraud and Increase Efficiency in Shared Services, 2013. (Box 4)
  - Certification of Agency Reconciliation to Dept. of Accounts (DOA) Reports, 2013, 2015. (Box 4)
  - 1st Annual Commonwealth IT Security Conference, 2014 Apr. (Box 4)
  - Dept. of Human Resource Management (DHRM) Report: Human Resources at a Glance, VITA Annual Report, 2014 June 30. (Box 4)
  - Public Safety Communications (PSC) Review - Internal Audit Final Report, 2014 Oct 7. (Box 4)
  - VITA Mission, Vision, Goals, 2014. (Box 4)
  - Computer Aid, Inc. (CAI) - IT Contingent Labor Status Reviews, 2014-2016. (Box 4)
  - Virginia State University (VSU) - Auditor of Public Accounts Audit Corrective Action, 2014-2016. (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia IT Projects Status Report - Summary, 2015 May. (Box 4)
  - VITA Update for Joing Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC), 2015 June 8. (Box 4)
  - Gartner Impact Assessment, 2015 July 17. (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Information Technology Symposium (COVITS), 2015 Sept. (Box 4)
  - VITA Strategic Plan, 2015 Nov 23. (Box 4)
  - Customer Advisory Council (CAC) - Introduction to VITA, VITA Update, and Role and Mission for CAC, 2015 Dec 9. (Box 4)
  - National Association of State Chief Information Officers (NASCIO) - 2015 State IT Recognition Awards, 2015 Best Practices in the Use of Information Technology in State Government, 2015. (Box 5)
  - VITA Strategic Plan, 2014-2016. (Box 5)
  - Election Preparation, 2015. (Box 5)
  - Virginia Dept. of Emergency Management (VDEM) - Correspondence, 2015. (Box 5)
  - Dept. of Taxation server patching, 2015, 2017. (Box 5)
  - Verizon security vulnerability, 2016 Apr 11. (Box 5)
  - VITA's Innovation Center of Excellence (ICE) Program - Presentation and Charter, 2016 Apr-Sept. (Box 5)
  - Virginia's Cyber Security Approach: Leadership through Diversity, 2016. (Box 5)
  - Social Security Administration audit, 2016. (Box 5)
  - Governor Terry McAuliffe - Data Analytic Summit, 2017 Apr 11. (Box 5)
  - VITA Agency Salary Administration Plan, 2017 July 14. (Box 5)
  - Higher Education Restructuring - Level II, Norfolk State University and Virginia State University, 2017. (Box 5)
  - Governor Transition, 2017. (Box 5)
  - VITA Succession Briefing Plan - Briefing to CIO, 2018. (Box 5)
  - CIO - Executive Team Agendas, 2018 Nov-2019 Aug. (Box 5)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Information Technology Symposium (COVITS), 2019 Sept. (Box 5)
  - Women in Innovation - Timeline and Project Closeout, 2019. (Box 5)